Hi, me in ten years.
I'm gonna schedule upload this video
ten years in the future.
So, you're gonna see this in 2025.
It's 2015 for me right now.
Dude, what if I'm dead?
Dude if I'm--
Ooh, that'd be weird.
That'd be so weird. RIP.
That would be really weird,
but let's see.
10-- dude, if I don't have a million
subscribers when you see this video,
my entire life has been a failure.
I hope I have a million subs.
I better have a million subscribers
when you guys see this.
But by the time you see this,
I'll have finished high school,
gone to college.
Probably be doing YouTube
as a job, hopefully. Maybe, maybe…
Um.
Yeah, uh, as of right now,
I'm enjoying YouTube.
Hopefully I still--
future me still enjoys it.
And, I don't know.
I'd-- be crazy
if I had some ridiculous amount
of subscribers.
At the time I’m recording this video,
I have 8000 subscribers
and 1.8 million views
So whenever you see this,
compare these numbers
to whatever I have
when you watch this.
Dude I really hope
I have a million subs by now.
Please future me, please.
What am I doing with my hand?
Please have a million subs.
I don’t--I probably should have
thought about what I was gonna say.
Just, hey, hopefully
you have a million subs.
And uh. Dude, I wonder if you still--
Okay, so I should be studying
for a history test.
And uh, I wonder if you and--
or me in ten years remembers
what grade I'm gonna get on this
history test that I take tomorrow,
that I'm not studying for
because I'm making these videos.
So I’m probably gonna do--
dude, if you still remember the grade
I get on this history test
in 10 years, that's crazy.
Dude, I'm probably gonna be married
and stuff, eh. Alright.
Oh watch me not be married
and not have a million subscribers,
not have any of this,
and then
you guys just think
I'm a big loser.
Then, yeah. I don't know.
Hopefully you're still doing YouTube.
Dude, what if I don't do YouTube
when this goes public?
That'd be weird.
What if I'm dead when you see this?
That'd be even weirder.
If you wanna, you want to see
what time it is,
just so you know
what the date is.
That’s the date.
Hopefully you can see that.
Hopefully you still do YouTube.
Um, yeah.
I don't know. Mmh.
Hey. Oh, my hair is messed up.
Alright, yeah.
I don't care.
Hey future me.
Hopefully you're having a good day.
So, yeah…
I better have a million
when this goes public.
Ten years, man.
Ten years.
I'm gonna be so different.
I really am gonna be so different.
Oh, man.
Man. Alright, well.
Alright, see you, guys.
See you, guys. See, me. Hey, me.
One last thing just so you know
what I'm talking about,
it's currently October 4th.
So uh, yeah. Like I said,
this is October fourth.